I’ll try to talk you through it
But I’m kinda locked in
With the way you’re moving
Everybody’s down, asking what
We’re doing
Funny we belong,
that’s according to ‘em
Yeah I know
You don’t really want to have to
Wait this long
But I think it’s better
And I think you know
Reading every message
And I can’t let go
Of what you’re saying on the outside
I’m trying not to fall to hard
I know
Can I just spill my guts?
Yeah we’re probably taking this
Too slow
Hoping I can speed it up
Why don’t we talk about it?
Got me saying too much
Ain’t no way around it
Why don’t we talk about it?
You know I’m the one, ain’t no need to doubt it
There ain’t no need to doubt it
Oh oh oh
Yeah I got you locked in too fast
Holding on my hand baby whiplash
What you want a new car, new bag?
Just know we’re running to the bank
Taking what you want, what you can’t have
Is a moment next to me til you say that
That’s my man, no other plan, let’s see you run that shit back
Let’s see you run that shit back
You cannot want what you have
Already saying it back
God damn I want you so bad
I wish we weren’t a match
It’s too late now I’m a mess
It’s time to step on the gas
Yeah I know
You don’t really want to have to
Wait this long
But I think it’s better
And I think you know
Reading every message
And I can’t let go
Of what you’re saying on the outside
I’m trying not to fall to hard
I know
Can I just spill my guts?
Yeah we’re probably taking this
Too slow
Hoping I can speed it up
Why don’t we talk about it?
Got me saying too much
Ain’t no way around it
Why don’t we talk about it?
You know I’m the one, ain’t no need to doubt it